FAHIM SIDDIQUI

ITCH.IO Profile: https://fahim97.itch.io/
Portfolio: https://fahim-97.github.io/

CONTACT

Email:

fahimsiddiqui1997@gmail.com

Phone: +1 647-574-0524 LinkedIn: fahimsiddigui97

SKILLS

Java, C#, Python Atom, Eclipse Android Studio Unity Game Engine

STRENGTHS

Determined individual
Fast learner
Sincere and hard-working
Customer Service Negotiations

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons.) Computer Science

Lassonde School of Engineering, York University, 2018 - Current

CERTIFICATION

MITx 6.00.1x, Introduction to Computer Science and Programming Using Python

AWARDS

AWARD RECEIVED

Provost's Award at Entrance, Lassonde School of Engineering

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A 4th Year Undergraduate Computer Science student at Lassonde School of Engineering. Experienced in video game development using Unity Game Engine. Open to innovative challenges in the practical fields of Computer Science and game development.

GAME DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

- Pestilence (Arcade style shooting game made in support of the countless victims of COVID-19 pandemic)
- Silver Lining (Text-based narrative game with 2D gameplay)
- Song of Hoop and Wire (Short 2D Arcade made after the Buzz
 Wire game)
- Why The Flowers Never Bloom (2D Platformer with hand-drawn style artwork and a recorded soundtrack)
- Kaito (2D RPG in development, Game Engine Footage available)
- Crooked Hearts (2D Role Playing Game with self-drawn concept arts)
- Breaking Block (A simple, satiric take on the classic block breaker game, made in protest of the global warming crisis)

WORK EXPERIENCES

Smart Systems Intern (January 2021 – April 2021)

Cortellucci Vaughan Hospital, Mackenzie Health

Responsibilities: Testing and maintaining the unique Smart Systems introduced in Canada's first Smart Hospital as a part of the co-op team from Lassonde.

Self-Checkout Attendant (2018 – 2020, May 2021 - Current)

Walmart Canada, Stockyards Supercenter, Toronto

Responsibilities: Familiarizing the customers with innovative additions to the store like Fast Lane and customer service at the Front-End.